all right time to cut through the
scientific jargon and give you my take
let's talk RAM cap right heads time to
talk broadheads Ram cap broadheads this
is the Hydra Shok right here this is a
hundred grain Hydra Shok this is what I
shoot currently today I started shooting
this about a year and a half two years
ago and I got to tell you the results
have been phenomenal now when I first
started shooting this fixed blade I was
a little bit worried about the tuning
process is it gonna fly straight it was
actually flawless now this is coming
from me I'm telling you the truth this
is how it happened I took the RAM cat
put it on the current arrow setup that I
have and within 15 shots I was dialed
right in up to 25 yards then I just
started backing up and tuned in my bow
to exactly what needed to happen that's
what I love about this broadhead is that
it flies straight and it is deadly it
really is I shot a buck in Kansas this
year at 30 yards full pastures so I've
never really had experience with the
back cut blade that they have here cuz
everything I've shot straight through
all right so let's open this up and
let's show you exactly what it is
so there's some specific features about
this broad head that absolutely need to
be called out first and foremost they're
sharp real sharp don't cut yourself
alright so there it is right there
look at that bad mamma-jamma that thing
is incredible alright so let's talk
about this broad head on an arrow I
actually have an arrow right here and I
want to show you how one of these
features that actually is one of the
biggest features of this broad head
concave scoop design Ram cat right here
the Hydra Shok basically takes all the
air flow and when it hits that concave
scoop it pushes it up and allows the air
to flow over top of those fletchings
right there which gives it absolutely no
drag as it's flying through the air that
is why they are the most accurate
deepest penetrating fix blade on the
market hey guys thanks for watching the
video if you like what you saw today you
want to learn more information check the
description below for
obviously go over to keep four brothers
calm cuz we're gonna have all kinds of
written word we're gonna have discounts
over there for you
and we've got lots of videos so check
that out and keep your brother's calm
and certainly if you like this video
subscribe to the channel because guess
what we're gonna bring you more content
just like this
[Music]